A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97) FA471
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A94), 1966-1994; 1.20; 217.2 Cubic Feet; Record cartons R2728-R2895, R2880A, R2896-R2902, R2905, R2906-R2911, R9402 and R9403.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 85013 A 407 - New York Public Library - Resident Fellows, 1984-1990 (Box R2875)
    - RF 85033 - University Of Pennsylvania - Race and the Legal Process, 1974-1991; 2 folders. (Box R2875)
    - RF 85033 - University Of Pennsylvania - Race and the Legal Process - Supplementary material (Box R2875)
    - RF 85047 A 6 - University of Ibadan - Norplant safety and sickle-cell anemia, 1986-1992 (Box R2876)
    - RF 85049 A 29 - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Monoclonal antibodies & sperm antigens, 1987-1991 (Box R2876)
    - RF 85049 A 30 - Peking University - Determinents of Fertility in China, 1988-1993 (Box R2876)
    - RF 85049 A 32 - Peking University - Population problems in rural China, 1988-1990 (Box R2876)
    - RF 85049 A 33 - University of Bahia - Estrogen progesterone receptor deficiency and infertile women, 1988-1991 (Box R2876)
    - RF 85049 A 35 - University of Chile - Steroid receptors in rat prostate, 1988-1989 (Box R2876)
    - RF 85049 A 35 - University of Chile - Steroid receptors in rat prostate - Supplementary material (Box R2876)
    - RF 85050 A 222 - Xavier University (Philippines) - Costello, 1985-1988, 1992 (Box R2876)
    - RF 85054 - Stanford University - U.S.-Mexican Relations, 1985-1990 (Box R2876)
    - RF 85054 - Stanford University - U.S.-Mexican Relations - Supplementary material (Box R2876)
    - RF 86026 - East-West Center - East West Population Institute - China Demography, 1985-1992 (Box R2877)
    - RF 86026 - East-West Center - East West Population Institute - China Demography - Supplementary material (Box R2877)
    - RF 86041 - Mozambique-Tanzania Centre For Foreig Relations - Regional Training & Security Studies, 1986-1991 (Box R2877)
    - RF 86058 A 50 - University of California - Apomixis in Rice, 1985-1989, 1992 (Box R2877)
    - RF 86058 A 61 - Washington State University - Rice Molecular Genetics, 1984-1992 (Box R2877)
    - RF 86059 A 6 - University of Missouri - Rice Wide Crossing Programs (Colombia), 1987-1991 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87001 A 23 - Rushemeza, Justin, 1987-1991 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87001 A 25 - Macwan'gi, Mubiana, 1987-1991 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87001 A 27 - Mazambani, David, 1987-1990 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87001 A 29 - Semali, Ladislaus M., 1988-1990 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87001 A 31 - Niameogo, Cyrille, 1987-1992 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87005 A 63 - Bhaya, Devaki, 1987-1991 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87006 A 104 - Universidad de Chile - Galdames, 1987-1990 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87006 A 112 - International Clinical Epidemiology Network - Sixth Annual Meeting, 1986-1988 (Box R2878)
    - RF 87026 A 4 - Tropical Forestry - Conference, 1985-1991, 1994 (Box R2879)
    - RF 87026 A 4 - Tropical Forestry - Conference - Supplementary material (Box R2879)
    - RF 87026 A 6 - Australian Centre for International Agricultural Research - Forestry Research, 1990-1993 (Box R2879)
    - RF 87031 A 23 - Survey Research Indonesia - Family Planning Services in Indonesia, 1989-1991 (Box R2879)
    - RF 87038 A 52 - Rosen, Ruth E., 1985-1990 (Box R2880)
    - RF 87043 - Strengthening Basic Skills - Testing, 1987-1991 (Box R2880)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1987-1993 (Box R2880)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation - Evaluation of Underclass Initiative (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1987 June (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1987 December (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1988 April (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1988 July (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1988 August (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1988 September (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1988 October (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1988 November (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1988 December (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 January (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 February (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 March (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 April (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 May (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 June (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 August (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 September (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 October (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 November (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1989 December (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation, 1990 (Box R2880A)
    - RF 87044 A 7 - Brandeis University - Community Planning and Action Projects Evaluation - Peer Review - Andrew Hahn (Box R2880A)
      Restricted from scholarly access.
    - RF 87056 A 252 - Poston, Dudley L., Jr., 1988-1992 (Box R2880)
    - RF 87058 A 67 - University of Tsukuba - Rice, 1986-1990 (Box R2880)
    - RF 88009 - South-to-South Cooperation in the Population Sciences - Bahia Conference, 1988-1989 (Box R2880)
    - RF 88009 - South-to-South Cooperation in the Population Sciences - Mombasa Conference, 1988 (Box R2880)
    - RF 88009 - South-to-South Cooperation in the Population Sciences - Santo Domingo Conference, 1989 March (Box R2881)
    - RF 88009 - South-to-South Cooperation in the Population Sciences - Villa Conference, 1987 September; 2 folders. (Box R2881)
    - RF 88009 - South-to-South Cooperation in the Population Sciences - Mateo de Acosta, 1986-1990 (Box R2881)
    - RF 88057 A 1 - Washington University- International Cassava Trans Project, 1988-1992 (Box R2881)
    - RF 88075 A 55 - Lihamba, Amandina, 1989-1990 (Box R2881)
    - RF 88077 A 3 - Academia Mexicana de Investigacio en Demografia Medica - Reproductive health and family planning, 1988-1994 (Box R2882)
    - RF 88077 A 3 - Academia Mexicana de Investigacio en Demografia Medica - Reproductive health and family planning - Supplementary material (Box R2882)
    - RF 89025 A 87 - Biotechnology and Rice Yield in Water Limited Conditions - Conference, 1988-1990 (Box R2882)
    - RF 89033 A 41 - Banaras Hindu University - Interspecific embryo transfer and pregnancy, 1988-1992 (Box R2882)
    - RF 89050 A 3 - Developing Countries Perspectives for Protecting the Global Commons - Conference, 1990-1991 (Box R2882)
    - RF 89055 A 33 - Becker, Laurence Cornell, 1988-1994 (Box R2882)
    - RF 89062 A 5 - Columbia University - HIV Research in Uganda, 1989-1992 (Box R2882)
    - RF 89062 A 8 - Johns Hopkins University - Serwadda's Training, 1990-1991 (Box R2882)
    - RF 89062 A 11 - University College (London) - AIDS research in Ivory Coast, 1990-1993 (Box R2882)
    - RF 89064 A 29 - World Bank- Family planning in tropical Africa, 1990-1991 (Box R2882)
    - RF 89065 Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists fellowships, 1985-1992; 4 folders. (Box R2883)
    - RF 89065 Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists fellowships, 1979-1984; 4 folders. (Box R2884)
    - RF 89065 Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists fellowships - Supplementary material (Box R2885)
    - RF 89067 A 29 - Lyon, Danny, 1989-1991 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 30 - McElwee, Ross, 1989-1993 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 33 - Lewis, Edward Tim, 1989-1991 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 34 - Tajima, Renee, 1989-1992 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 36 - Massiah, Louis J., 1989-1992 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 38 - Schwartz, Jon, 1989-1991 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 39 - Nelson, Gunvor, 1989-1992 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 42 - Downey, Juan, 1989-1993 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 43 - Buba, Tony, 1988-1994 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 44 - Burnett, Charles, 1987, 1990-1993 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 45 - Choy, Christine, 1988-1993 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 46 - Dash, Julie, 1988-1993 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 47 - Garcia, Ana Maria, 1988-1993 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 48 - Gerima, Haile, 1987-1992 (Box R2886)
    - RF 89067 A 49 - Godmilow, Jill, 1988-1991 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 50 - Halleck, DeeDee, 1988-1994 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 51 - Hill, Gary, 1988-1993 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 52 - Kos, Paul, 1987-1991 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 53 - Marshall, John K., 1988-1991 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 54 - Masayesva, Victor, Jr., 1987-1991 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 55 - Trinh T. Minh-ha, 1987-1991 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 56 - Oliver, Enrique, 1988-1993 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 57 - Portillo, Lourdes, 1987, 1990-1992 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 58 - Rainer, Yvonne, 1987-1991 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 59 - Bourne, St. Clair, 1988-1993 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 60 - Riggs, Marlon T., 1988-1993 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 61 - Thornton, Leslie, 1988-1993 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 62 - Woodberry, Billy, 1988-1993 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89067 A 63 - Jonas, Joan, 1989-1993 (Box R2887)
    - RF 89073 A 3 - New Haven Public Schools - Consortium for Urban Education, 1989-1993 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89073 A 8 - Howard University - Comer Implementation in DC, 1990-1992 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89076 A 3 - Resolution, Inc. - New Audiences and Markets for African Films, 1990-1991 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89076 A 4 - Foundation for Independent Video Film, Inc. - "Independent Producer's Guide to Film & Video Distributors", 1990-1991 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89076 AID - Media for Development International - Docudramas Broadcast Strategy, 1990-1992 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89077 - American Assembly - Role of the Arts in the U.S., 1989-1991 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89077 - American Assembly - Role of the Arts in the U.S. - Supplementary material (Box R2888)
    - RF 89078 A 21 - Jerusalem El-Hakawati for Theatre & Visual Arts - "In Search of Omar Khayyam", 1989-1993 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89078 A 22 - Brava! for Women in the Arts - "Shadow of a Man", 1989-1994 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89078 A 23 - Eureka Theatre, Inc. - "Shadow of a Man", 1989, 1993-1994 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89078 A 24 - Japan Performing Arts Center - "Outrage the Limits of Man" production, 1989-1992 (Box R2888)
    - RF 89086 - International Councll of Nurses - Nursing Professionalization workshop, 1988-1992 (Box R2889)
    - RF 89090 A 6 - Health Transition - Development Activities, 1990-1992 (Box R2889)
    - RF 89091 - South-to-South Cooperation in the Population Sciences - Egypt Conference, 1989 November (Box R2889)
    - RF 89091 - South-to-South Cooperation in the Population Sciences - Egypt Conference - Supplementary material (Box R2889)
    - RF 89091 A 43 - Asociacion Dominicana Pro-Bienstar de la Familja, Inc. - Anti-LHRH vaccine trial, 1990-1993 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89091 A 46 - University of Mexico - Antiprogestin steroid drug, 1989-1991 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89091 A 48 - University of Zimbabwe - Population clinical trials, 1987-1992 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89091 A 49 - Centro de Pesquisa e Assistencia em Reproducao Humana- Contraceptive trials, 1987-1992 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89091 A 50 - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Gossypol as gynecological agent, 1990-1991 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89091 A 52 - National Institute of Nutrition Salvador Zubiran (Mexico City) Gossypol & men infected with HIV, 1989-1992 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89091 A 54 - University of Lagos - Contraceptive counseling, 1987-1992 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89092 A 64 - Ogum, G.E.D., 1989-1993 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89092 A 65 - Makerere University - High fertility determinents, 1989-1993 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89092 A 66 - National Museums of Kenya - Monoclonal antibodies workshop, 1989-1992 (Box R2890)
    - RF 89092 A 69 - Nigerian Fertility Society - Fertility regulation conference, 1990-1993 (Box R2891)
    - RF 89092 A 70 - Addis Ababa University - Reproductive biology course in Uganda, 1990-1991 (Box R2891)
    - RF 89092 A 72 - Commonwealth Regional Health Community Secretariat for East, Central & Southern Africa - Contraceptive use and health of African women, 1990-1993 (Box R2891)
    - RF 89092 A 75 - Princeton University - Fertility transition in Africa, 1990-1992 (Box R2891)
    - RF 89092 A 76 - Onokerhoraye, Andrew G., 1989-1992 (Box R2891)
    - RF 89092 A 79 - Ifeka, Caroline, 1990-1993 (Box R2891)
    - RF 89092 A 88 - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population - Fertility transition in Sub-Saharan Africa Seminar, 1991-1992 (Box R2891)
    - RF 89092 A 88 - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population - Fertility transition in Sub-Saharan Africa Seminar - Supplementary material, 2 folders. (Box R2891)
    - RF 89092 A 89 - Oni, Gbolahan A., 1987-1992 (Box R2892)
    - RF 89092 A 93 - Africa Press Trust - Population and Media Workshop, 1990-1993 (Box R2892)
    - RF 89093 A 264 - Wong, Rebecca, 1989-1992 (Box R2892)
    - RF 89093 A 265 - Fricke, Thomas E., 1989-1992 (Box R2892)
    - RF 89093 A 268 - Mahidol University - Child Care and Women's Status in Urban Thailand, 1989-1993 (Box R2892)
    - RF 89094 A 2 - Power, Alison G., 1991-1992 (Box R2892)
    - Task Force for Development - Books and Articles, 1984-1986 (Box R9402)
    - Task Force for Development - Books and Articles, 1984-1986 (Box R9403)
    - RF 89095 - World Resources Institute - Developing Countries Agricultural Policies, 1989-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2893)
    - RF 89098 - Social Science Research Council - African Agriculture, 1984-1992; 2 folders. (Box R2893)
    - RF 89100 A 4 - Female Participation in African Education - Workshop, 1990-1993 (Box R2894)
    - RF 89100 A 8 - Makerere University - Minds across (Literacy Program), 1990-1994 (Box R2894)
    - RF 90010 - Emory University - Public Health Minority Fellows, 1986-1993 (Box R2894)
    - RF 90013 A 18 - IAF BioVac, Inc. - Viral vaccine production and accessibility, 1990-1992 (Box R2894)
    - RF 90055 A 5 - Mexican Health Foundation - Aedes Aegypti control program, 1990-1992 (Box R2894)
    - RF 91001 A 127 - University of Perpignan - Rice breeding, 1985-1992 (Box R2896)
    - RF 91001 A 130 - University of Leiden - Rice genetic manipulation, 1984-1991; 2 folders. (Box R2896)
    - RF 91002 A 6 - International Rice Research Institute - Training Workshop, 1990-1992 (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 82 - Bai Yongyan, 1990-1992 (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 84 - Sarma, Nukala Padmanabha, 1990-1992 (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 87 - Li Xiu-Qing, 1990-1992 (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 99 - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) - Training course in Rice Biotechnology, 1990-1991 (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 99 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Rice Biotechnology Training Course, 1990-1992 (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 114- Wang Gouliang, 1991-1993 (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 117 - RF Fifth Annual Meeting on Rice Biotechnology, 1991-1992 (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 117 - RF Fifth Annual Meeting on Rice Biotechnology - Supplementary material (Box R2897)
    - RF 91003 A 118 - Li Liangcai, 1990-1993 (Box R2898)
    - RF 91004 A 2 - Center for Environmental & Agricultural Policy Research, Extension and Development - Rice production constraints, 1991-1993 (Box R2898)
    - RF 91004 A 3 - International Rice Research Institute - Rice prioritization, 1991-1992 (Box R2898)
    - RF 91009 A 4 - Makerere University - Use and fat of pesticides in Uganda, 1991-1994 (Box R2898)
    - RF 91013 A 478 - Fellowships - Humanities - Evaluation conference, 1991-1992 (Box R2898)
    - RF 91014 A 14 - Festival International de Louisiane - Foreign participants, 1989-1993 (Box R2898)
    - RF 91014 A 18 - New York International Festival of the Arts - 1991 artists, 1990-1992 (Box R2898)
    - RF 91014 A 19 - Santa Fe Chamber Music Festival, Ltd. - Music of the Americas, 1988-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2899)
    - RF 91014 A 19 - Santa Fe Chamber Music Festival, Ltd. - Music of the Americas - Supplementary material (Box R2899)
    - RF 91014 A 20 -Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, Inc. - 1991 International Programs, 1991-1992 (Box R2899)
    - RF 91014 A 22 - Movement Theatre International - African & Asian Artists, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box R2899)
    - RF 91014 A 23 - University of the Arts - "Festival Mythos", 1990-1992 (Box R2899)
    - RF 91014 A 25 - New York Shakespeare Festival (Public Theatre) Latino Festival, 1984-1992; 3 folders. (Box R2900)
    - RF 91014 A 25 - New York Shakespeare Festival (Public Theatre) Latino Festival - Supplementary material (Box R2900)
    - RF 91014 A 26 - Contemporary Arts Center, Inc. (New Orleans) - Live Arts Festival, 1991, 1994 (Box R2900)
    - RF 91014 A 27 - Theater for the New City Foundation, Inc. - Eco-Festival in New York, 1990-1993 (Box R2900)
    - RF 91014 A 28 - City Lore, Inc. - "Island Roots - Mainland Branches", 1991-1993 (Box R2901)
    - RF 91014 A 29 - Brooklyn Academy of Music - 1992 Israeli festival, 1991-1994 (Box R2901)
    - RF 91015 A 43 - Crafts Report Educational Fund - "Crafts: pathways to cultures", 1990-1991 (Box R2901)
    - RF 91016 A 8 - Southern Regional Council - Redistricting & Minorities (Southern Project), 1990-1991 (Box R2902)
    - RF 91023 - University of Michigan - Legal Assistance for Urban Communties, 1990-1994 (Box R2902)
    - RF 91025 A 88 - American Forum - New York City Schools and Cultural Institutions, 1983-1994; 4 folders. (Box R2905)
    - RF 91025 A 88 - American Forum - New York City Schools and Cultural Institutions - Supplementary material (Box R2905)
    - RF 91025 A 91 - Pittsburgh - Education - Teacher Training in Arts and Humanities, 1983-1994 (Box R2906)
    - RF 91025 A 91 - Pittsburgh - Education - Teacher Training in Arts and Humanities - Supplementary material (Box R2906)
    - RF 91025 A 94 - South Carolina Committee for the Humanities - REACH Program and School-based and State-wide reforms, 1991-1993 (Box R2906)
    - RF 91026 - Committee for South African Development, 1991-1993 (Box R2906)
    - RF 91026 A 2 - Phelps Stokes Fund for South African Development, 1990-1992 (Box R2906)
    - RF 91030 A 1 - Task Force for Child Survival Vaccine Development Project, 1988-1993 (Box R2906)
    - RF 91031 A 293 - University of Chile - Diaz, 1991-1993 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 296 - University of Zimbabwe -Wellington, 1990-1993 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 301 - Suez Canal University - Hamam, 1991 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 303 - Makerere University - Karamagi, 1991-1993 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 306 - International Clinical Epidemiology Network - Social Science and Biostatistics Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 308 - Makerere University - Lubanga, 1991-1994 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 312 - Shanghai Medical University - Clinical Epidemiology Unit, 1986-1992 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 315 - Makerere University - Clinical Epidemiology Study (Mulago Hospital), 1991-1993 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 317 - University of Health Sciences - Madras Clinical Epidemiology Unit, 1984-1993 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 317 - University of Health Sciences - Madras Clinical Epidemiology Unit - Supplementary material (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 318 - University of the Philippines - Health Social Science Workshop, 1991-1992 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 319 - University of Yaounde - Kouda Zeh, 1991-1992 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 321 - International Epidemiological Association - Southeast Asia Regional Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 324 - Suez Canal University - Diab, 1991-1993 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 327 - Moi University - Anabwani, 1990-1993 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 328 - Moi University - Menya, 1990-1993 (Box R2909)
    - RF 91031 A 339 - University of Zimbabwe - Clinical Epidemiology Unit, 1987-1993 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91035 A 5 - New Gate Ventures - Energy efficient windows in Ukraine, 1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91036 A 3 - Conservation Co. Establish Willy Brandt International Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 197 - Konate, Yacouba, 1990-1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 203 - Van Wyk, Gary, 1990-1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 205 - Kebede, Eilene, 1991-1993 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 207 - Wegulo, Francis N., 1991-1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 214 - Musi, Patricia Jabu, 1991-1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 218 - Mulinge, Munyae Masai, 1991-1994 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 222 - Okolie, Andrew C., 1991-1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 224 - Seethal, Cecil, 1991-1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 227 - Olaleye, Oyewole, 1991-1993 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 235 - Boadi, Isaac Opoku, 1988-1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 242 - Cole, Roddie- African Dissertation Internship Award, 1991-1992 (Box R2910)
    - RF 91037 A 246 - Ombakho, George - African Dissertation Internship Award, 1991-1992 (Box R2911)
    - RF 91037 A 262 - Clark University - African Dissertation Internship Awards Recognition Grant, 1992 (Box R2911)
    - RF 91038 A 1 - Mediators Foundation, Inc. - Partners project and Armswatch, 1989-1992 (Box R2911)
    - RF 91039 - Kroyt Brandt Productions, Inc. - "1492 - Clash of Visions" TV series, 1990-1993 (Box R2911)
    - RF 91040 A 75 - Colorado Dance Festival, Inc. - Interdisciplinary artists, 1989-1991 (Box R2911)
    - RF 91049 A 7 - Community Development Collaborative - National Community Development, 1989-1991 (Box R2911)
    - RF 91052 - Banco Sol - Microenterprise Banking, 1990-1992 (Box R2911)
    - RF 91053 - Long Bow Group, Inc. - "Gate of Heavenly Peace" China TV documentary, 1991-1994 (Box R2911)
    - RF 91060 A 6 - InternationalCenter for Tropical Agriculture - Travel support for speakers to attend meeting, 1992-1993 (Box R2911)
  - Fellowships
    - ABEYKOON, Anthony, 1985-1987 (Box R2803)
    - AKANDE, Bolanle E., 1987-1990 (Box R2803)
    - ATEMIE, Josiah Dagogo, 1984-1987 (Box R2803)
    - BANDIV DEKAR, Atamaram, 1986-1990 (Box R2803)
    - BAUNI, Evasius K., 1989-1990 (Box R2803)
    - BEN Kunlong, 1985-1989 (Box R2803)
    - BHARGAVA, Pradeep Kumar, 1987-1993 (Box R2803)
    - BHASSORN Limanonda, 1985-1987 (Box R2803)
    - BHATTACHARYYA, Amitabha, 1984-1989 (Box R2803)
    - BOONSIRM Withyachumnarnkul, 1987-1990 (Box R2803)
    - DAHAL, Ganesh, 1988-1992 (Box R2803)
    - DAI Rong-xi, 1982-1987 (Box R2803)
    - DE SILVA, Weraduwage Indralal, 1989-1991 (Box R2804)
    - DIOP, Francois, 1988-1990 (Box R2804)
    - FARES, Fuad, 1988-1992 (Box R2804)
    - GANGRADE, Bhushan Kumar, 1985-1989 (Box R2804)
    - GHOSH, Debabrata, 1988-1991 (Box R2804)
    - Guo Shenyang, 1987-1991 (Box R2804)